<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Examen</string>
    <string name="dailyquiz">Daily quiz</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- sub activities  -->
    <string name="sub_daily">Daily Quiz</string>
    <string name="sub_interview">Interview</string>
    <string name="sub_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="sub_technews">News</string>

    <!-- login google button -->
    <string name="google_sign_up">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="text_info">Make sure you have good Internet connection</string>
    <string name="text_infos">Google Sign in required for Authentication Purpose</string>
    <string name="appname">Examen</string>
    <string name="logo_image">App Logo</string>

    <!-- notification -->

    <string name="notify_text">Coming soon...</string>
    <!-- header navigation menu -->
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="tech_news">Tech News</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="like_us">Like us on Facebook</string>
    <string name="about_developer">About Developer</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us:-mathuranant@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- Content Navigation or change this placeholder text-->
    <string name="daily_quiz">Daily Quiz</string>
    <string name="Interview">Interview</string>
    <!-- content language describation -->
    <string name="c_program">C Program</string>
    <string name="resultall">Result Quiz</string>


    <!-- content submenu describation -->
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="smart_point_sname">QuizApp</string>
    <string name="str_next">Next</string>

    <!-- content of interview fresher experience -->
    <string name="freshers">Freshers</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="interview">Interview</string>
    <string name="technical">Technical</string>

    <string name="not_close_session">notclose_session</string>

    <!--    news content description -->
    <string name="title">This is news title</string>
    <string name="description">This is news description</string>
    <string name="author">News Author</string>
    <string name="newstime">Time</string>
    <string name="imagedescription">Tech News</string>

    <!-- home fragment resource -->
    <string name="python">Python</string>
    <string name="android">Android</string>
    <string name="java">Java</string>
    <string name="cprogram">CProgram</string>
    <string name="back_arrow">back_arrow</string>

    <!--- header navigation -->
    <string name="profile_gmail">Gmail Profile</string>
    <string name="gmailName">examen@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="dis_username">Examen</string>

    <!-- menu setting -->
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <!---  Notification  -->
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming soon..</string>
    <string name="notificationImg">Notification Image</string>


    <string name="question_quiz">Question: 1/x</string>
    <string name="qestion_text">Here will be the question text\nHere will be the question text\nHere will be the question text"
        </string>

    <!---  about us   -->
    <string name="app_version">App Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="description_app">
        App enable you to play quiz from different computer languages.
        We show Result of each question after completion of quiz.
        six language are active now like Android, Java, C, Sqlite, Python,
        ReactJS, Machine Learning.in feature we are going to active more languages for you.
        You can Share the app with your friends.
    </string>
    <string name="photos">Photos</string>
    <string name="Result">Result</string>
    <string name="Retest">Retest</string>
    <!-- Quiz radio button value -->
    <string name="radiobuttona">RadioButtonA</string>
    <string name="radiobuttonb">RadioButtonB</string>
    <string name="radiobuttonc">RadioButtonC</string>


    <!-- fresher quiz -->
    <string name="fresher">Fresher Quiz</string>
    <string name="a_question">1.Tell me about Yourself?</string>
    <string name="a_ans">My name is gaurav kumar mathur I belongs
        to Rajasthan and I am doing Btech in Computer science.
        </string>

    <string name="b_question">2.What is your greatest weakness?</string>
    <string name="b_ans">I can not say no when someone ask for help
      and i am a bit lazy about which i am not interested </string>

    <string name="c_question">3.How do you handle stress and pressure??</string>
    <string name="c_ans">stress is very important to me because
        I do best under stress and pressure.
        I’ve found that I really enjoy working in a challenging environment.</string>

    <string name="d_question">4.Why should we hire you?</string>
    <string name="d_ans">Sir,as I am a fresher,i have theoretical knowledge but
        I can do hard work for my organization.And I will put all my efforts
        for the good progress of organization.Being punctual ans sincere,
        I can finish the work given to me on time and try
        my best to fulfill and the needs of company from me.</string>

    <string name="e_question">5.Why do you want to work here?</string>
    <string name="e_ans"> Sir, it is a great privilege for anyone to work in a reputed company like yours.
        When I read about your company I found that my skills are matching your requirements.
        Here I can showcase my skills to contribute to the company growth.</string>

    <string name="f_question">6.What do you know about the company?</string>
    <string name="f_ans"> It is one of best growing company in india.The work
        environment of company is very good.People feel proud to be
        part of the company as company provide full support to their
        employess in professinal front it has many branches across the world so
        I have good opportunity to show my talent</string>

    <string name="g_question">7.What are your salary requirements?</string>
    <string name="g_ans"> I am fresher.Salary is not first priority for me.
        this is a big platform to start my career and i also want to
        improve my knowledge and skill and gain experience.
        so i expect a considerable of salary according to my ability
        and your company's norms which will fulfill my economical need.</string>

    <string name="h_question">8.What are your career goals?</string>
    <string name="h_ans">My short term goal is to get a job in reputed company where i can utilize my skills and improve my career path.
        My long term goal is be in respectable position in that organization. .</string>

    <string name="i_question">9.Tell me what you know about this company?</string>
    <string name="i_ans">Tit is one of best growing comapny in india.The work
              environment of company is very good.People feel proud to be
          part of the company as company provide full support to their employess in professinal front
           it has many branches across the world so I have good opportunity to show my talent.</string>

    <string name="j_question">10.Give me an example of your creativity? </string>
    <string name="j_ans">My creativity is l have learned from my mistakes,
        I do try to make failures in success. even I believe that failure is stepping stone of success.
        failures are always big lessons from life.</string>

    <string name="k_question">11.How do you feel about working nights and weekend?</string>
    <string name="k_ans">I am a fresher and energetic. I have a no problem to do work late nights.
        but I will try my best to finish my work within the working hours.
        and I believe in your company and if the company is demanding me,
        then there is some reason behind that and i can assist my company as I can.
    </string>

    <string name="l_question">12.What motivates you?</string>
    <string name="l_ans">Primarily, my ability to work hard and delivering result motivates me.
        But subsequent recognition of my efforts gives me the encouragement for my next efforts.
    </string>


    <string name="n_question">13.Where do you see yourself in 5 years?</string>
    <string name="n_ans"> In five years’ time, I see myself growing along with the team,
        developing and using new skills to the benefit of the organization.
        I find this position extremely motivating and exciting.
        I can imagine many challenges lying ahead of me, which I am excited to experience.
        And therefore, I am eager to invest my five years time learning all
        facets of the job towards professional advancement.</string>


    <string name="m_question">14.Your interview is more or less coming to an end when the interviewer asks you,
        “Do you have any questions for me?” </string>
    <string name="m_ans"> “How has your journey been so far in this organization?
        What excites you the most about working here?
        How long does it ideally take a person to prove their caliber here?
        Where is the organization headed in the next years?
        What are the next steps of this interview?” </string>


    <!-- experience  question -->
    <string name="experience_quiz">Experience Quiz</string>
    <!-- quiz 1-->
    <string name="a_questions">1.Tell me about Yourself?</string>
    <string name="a_answer"> My name is gaurav kumar mathur.I am doinf Btech in Computer
        Science. I have 1 year experience in Android Developement and we are four
        member in my family includeing me.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 2 -->
    <string name="b_questions">2.What should I hire you?</string>
    <string name="b_answer">With reference to my work experience,I Satisfy all the requirement
          for this job. I am sincere with my work and would never let you down in anyway.
          I promise you will never regret for the decision to appoint me in your organization.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 3-->
    <string name="c_questions">3.What are your salary requirements?</string>
    <string name="c_answer">I have 2 years of experience in Android developement
           field.My current ctc is 3.5 lpa salary has never been a big issues for me.
           Still I am expecting salary as company norms as per my designation and my
           qualification and experience which can help me to maintain the standard of
           level of my personal and economical needs.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 4 -->
    <string name="d_questions">4.What are your career goals?</string>
    <string name="d_answer">My short term goal is to get a job in reputed company where
            I can utilize my skills and improve my career path. My long term goal is be
            in respectable position in that organization.
   </string>

    <!-- quiz 5 -->
    <string name="e_questions">5.Did you have any failures in your life?</string>
    <string name="e_answer">I failed to score a good percentage in my graduation .
             I work hard for it but I scored less than what I expected.when I think
             about percentage there will always regret for me.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 6 -->
    <string name="f_questions">6.What are your Weakness?</string>
    <string name="f_answer">I can  say yes when someone ask for help
             and I am a bit lazy about which i am not interested.
             Straightforward
             Impatient
             Sensitive Trust people very quickly
             note: you should tell only two or three Weakness
     </string>
    <!-- quiz 7 -->
    <string name="g_questions">7.Why are you looking for a job change?</string>
    <string name="g_answer">I have learnt a lot of things from there. According
          to me change are necessary for everyone to enhance your skills, knowledge
          and for personal growth and financial growth. Your organization is the good
          platform where I can learn more.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 8 -->
    <string name="h_questions">8.Why are you interested in working for our Company?</string>
    <string name="h_answer">I have wanted to work in this organization for a long time now,
        so when I heard about a vacancy in your company that fit my profile,
        I immediately applied for it. I admire the way you successfully combine commerce
        with socially responsible business and would love to be a part of an organization
        that looks at business in a holistic manner.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 9 -->
    <string name="i_questions">9.Why do you want to leave your current company?</string>
    <string name="i_answer">I have put in a number of years in my current organization,
        performed well and risen through the ranks, but I would now like something more
        challenging.I believe this job will provide me with exactly such an opportunity.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 10 -->
    <string name="j_questions">10. What can you offer us that someone else cannot?</string>
    <string name="j_answers">I have already mentioned my strengths, but if you were to ask me
        about something unique which I bring, I would say it is my attention to detail.
        Though it can be annoying for others, this trait of mine has saved several situations
        from turning into disasters in the past.
    </string>

    <!-- quiz 11 -->
    <string name="k_questions">11. Tell us about an accomplishment you are most proud of?</string>
    <string name="k_answer">I am extremely proud of the time we worked on a project with Microsoft company.
        The selection was a gruelling process, but we managed to land the deal. The company needed services
        that were of the highest standards and I am proud to say that we surpassed their expectations.
        In fact, we succeeded in converting them into our regular clients. As project member
        I was extremely proud of this achievement.
    </string>
    <!-- quiz 13 -->

    <string name="n_questions">13.How do you handle failure?</string>
    <string name="n_answer">I have always lived by the maxim that nobody is perfect, so I am relatively comfortable taking
        responsibility for my shortcomings. My approach is to figure out what I could change to avoid similar circumstances
        in the future
    </string>

    <!-- quiz 14 -->
    <string name="m_questions">14.What is your philosophy towards work??</string>
    <string name="m_answer">I have only one philosophy when it comes to work: every piece of work, regardless of size, has
            to be done on time and in the right manner.</string>
    <string name="score_0">Score: 0</string>
    <string name="_00_30">00:30</string>
    <string name="option_1">Option 1</string>
    <string name="option_2">Option 2</string>
    <string name="option_3">Option 3</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="following">Following</string>
    <string name="followers">Followers</string>
    <string name="mathuranant123gmail_com">mathuranant123@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="follow_me">Follow Me</string>
    <string name="gaurav_mathur">Gaurav Kumar Mathur</string>
    <string name="gaurav_mathur_profile">Gaurav Kumar Mathur</string>
    <string name="followings">Following</string>
    <string name="followers_8">11</string>
    <string name="followers_github">Followers</string>
    <string name="_522">26</string>
    <string name="github_profile">Github</string>
    <string name="following_7">8</string>
    <string name="email">email_developer</string>
    <string name="follow_mes">Follow Me</string>
    <string name="gauravmathur_gmail">mathuranant123@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="_7_21">8</string>
    <string name="facebook_sign_up">Facebook Sign Up</string>


</resources>
